[
    {
        "question": "Who is the Vice-Chancellor?",
        "answer": "Dr. Manmohan Singh Chauhan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the contact number of Dr. Manmohan Singh Chauhan?",
        "answer": "05944-233333, 7500122224"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fax number for the Vice-Chancellor?",
        "answer": "05944-233500"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the PS to V.C.?",
        "answer": "Shri G.S. Patwal"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the contact number of Shri G.S. Patwal?",
        "answer": "05944-233333"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fax number for the PS to V.C.?",
        "answer": "05944-233663"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the intercom number of Shri G.S. Patwal?",
        "answer": "4444"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Registrar?",
        "answer": "Dr. Deepa Vinay"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the contact number of Dr. Deepa Vinay?",
        "answer": "05944-233640"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fax number for the Registrar?",
        "answer": "05944-233640"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the intercom number of Dr. Deepa Vinay?",
        "answer": "4379"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the PS to Registrar?",
        "answer": "Shri P. C. Joshi"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the contact number of Shri P. C. Joshi?",
        "answer": "05944-233640"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fax number for the PS to Registrar?",
        "answer": "05944-233640"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the intercom number of Shri P. C. Joshi?",
        "answer": "4301"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Dy. Registrar?",
        "answer": "Dr. Anjali Choudhary"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the contact number of Dr. Anjali Choudhary?",
        "answer": "7500241538"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fax number for the Dy. Registrar?",
        "answer": "---"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the intercom number of Dr. Anjali Choudhary?",
        "answer": "4378"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Dean, PGS?",
        "answer": "Dr. Kiran P. Raverkar"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the contact number of Dr. Kiran P. Raverkar?",
        "answer": "05944-233326"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fax number for the Dean, PGS?",
        "answer": "05944-233473"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the intercom number of Dr. Kiran P. Raverkar?",
        "answer": "4357"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Dean, College of Agriculture?",
        "answer": "Dr. S.K. Kashyap"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the contact number of Dr. S.K. Kashyap?",
        "answer": "05944-233632"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fax number for the Dean, College of Agriculture?",
        "answer": "05944-233257"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the intercom number of Dr. S.K. Kashyap?",
        "answer": "4450"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Dean, College of Agribusiness Management?",
        "answer": "Dr. R.S. Jadoun"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the contact number of Dr. R.S. Jadoun?",
        "answer": "05944-233884"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fax number for the Dean, College of Agribusiness Management?",
        "answer": "05944-233533"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the intercom number of Dr. R.S. Jadoun?",
        "answer": "4365"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Dean, College of Basic Sciences & Humanities?",
        "answer": "Dr. Sandeep Arora"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the contact number of Dr. Sandeep Arora?",
        "answer": "+91-7055470555"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fax number for the Dean, College of Basic Sciences & Humanities?",
        "answer": "05944-233374"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the intercom number of Dr. Sandeep Arora?",
        "answer": "4491"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Dean, College of Fisheries?",
        "answer": "Dr. Avdhesh Kumar"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the contact number of Dr. Avdhesh Kumar?",
        "answer": "05944-233377"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fax number for the Dean, College of Fisheries?",
        "answer": "05944-233377"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Dean, College of Community Science?",
        "answer": "Dr. Alka Goel"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the contact number of Dr. Alka Goel?",
        "answer": "05944-233637"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fax number for the Dean, College of Community Science?",
        "answer": "05944-233637"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Dean, College of Technology?",
        "answer": "Dr. S.S. Gupta"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the contact number of Dr. Alaknanda Ashok?",
        "answer": "05944-233338"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fax number for the Dean, College of Technology?",
        "answer": "05944-233338"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Dean, College of Veterinary & Animal Sciences?",
        "answer": "Dr. A.H. Ahmad"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the contact number of Dr. A.H. Ahmad?",
        "answer": "05944-233347"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the intercom number of Dr. A.H. Ahmad?",
        "answer": "4402"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the Dean, Student Welfare?",
        "answer": "Dr. A.S. Jeena"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the contact number of Dr. A.S. Jeena?",
        "answer": "05944-233536"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fax number for the Dean, Student Welfare?",
        "answer": "05944-233536"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the intercom number of Dr. A.S. Jeena?",
        "answer": "4377"
    }
]